





# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

# Summary

Last Active: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Production Support experience in J2EE development environment.

Monitor process and software changes that impact production support, communicate project information to the production support team and raise production support issues to the project team.

Perform production support activities which involves assignment of issues and issue analysis and resolution within the specified SLAs.

Provide daily support with resolution of escalated tickets to ensure issues are resolved in timely manner.

Suggest fixes to complex issues by doing a thorough analysis of root cause and impact of the defect.

Solid experience in developing and supporting applications including scripting skills in perl, Unix Shell scripting.

Experience in Incident Management, Change Management and Problem Management.

Experience in Configuration and Release Management.

Oracle query development, strong PL/SQL skills, knowledge of Data Modeling.

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Strong Database troubleshooting experience on Oracle database.

#### **Work Experience**

- IBM India Pvt. Ltd as Sr. Java Production support Analyst Apr 2010 to Jun 2017
- Tech Mahindra Ltd as Technical Associate Nov 2006 to Aug 2007
- ITC Infotech India Pvt. Ltd as Associate IT Consultant Feb 2005 to Nov 2006

^ Back to Top

## Education

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (Computers) from Sri Venkateshwara University (SVU), Tirupati in 2000

^ Back to Top

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Windows, Linux, Solaris	
Java, C	
IDRC ISP Sanlets Filh	

0000, 001, 001 v1010, 1150	
Oracle 9i, DB2,SQL Server	
Struts2.0, Spring, Hibernate	
HTML, XML, JavaScript, CSS, Ajax, Jquery	
Tomcat, Weblogic, WebSphere	
Edipse, RSA	

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.